(Leonard:)Seconded.
I was gonna put down a towel.
(Raj:)I still want it on my balcony.
I say we move it on a bimonthly basis.
- That sounds fair.
- Hold on. Bimonthly is an ambiguous term.
(Sheldon:)- Every other month or twice a month?
- Twice a month.
- Then no.
- Okay, every other month.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you can't be selfish.
(Leonard:)We all paid for it,
so it belongs to all of us.
Now get out of the way
so I can sit in my time machine.
[ALL GASPING]
(Leonard:)Okay. I am setting the dials
for March 10th, 1876.
(Howard:)Good choice. Alexander Graham Bell
invents the telephone and calls for Watson.
- Wait a minute. I wanna see that too.
- So when it's your turn, you can.
If we all go back to the same time,
Bell's lab's going to get very crowded.
(Sheldon:)He'll know something's up.
(Raj:)Since the time machine
doesn't move in space...
(Raj:)- ...you'll end up in 1876 Pasadena.
- Even if you make it to Boston...